

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Front end developer with 3+ years of experience, ambitious individual with a passion for learning and creativity. Hardworking candidate possessing strong analytical problem solving skill. Looking to leverage my knowledge and experience into a role as a frontend developer.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Jet Support Services LTD, Lagos / June 2023 - Present

- Collaborated with a back-end developer to conceive and construct an innovative Airline Flight Technical Log.
- My pivotal role revolved around designing and consuming the back-end API, and creating stunning cutting edge designs.
- To develop a digital aircraft technical logbook, which i utilized various frontend technology, including React, Zustand, React Query and Typescript etc.
- By leveraging my expertise in frontend development, I have contributed to the creation of a robust and efficient solution that enhances operational efficiency within the aviation domain.

INTERSHIP (Junior Software Developer)

Chams PLC, Ikeja, Lagos / May 2021 - October 2021

- Assisted in deploying their Saas called VOTA, and it's database
- I represented the company at NNPC 2021 election where I was opportune to coordinate and monitor the system process, the system network architecture.
- Conducted quality assurance checks on products before release in the market
- Acquired knowledge in web development and design principles while creating content for web applications.

Contact: Mr Wale - +234 816 985 8606.

CONTACTS

Email:

olamidemoraks@gmail.com

Phone: 0810 0311 867

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SASS
Tailwind CSS,
Javascript,Typescript
React js,Redux,
Next js, Node js,
Mongo db, Angular

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S)

Landmark university, kwar 2018 - 2022 GPA 3.7